pdc.tv 2018-06-27

# Privacy Policy | PDC

In general, you may visit this Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. Our servers collect the domain names, operating system in use (e.g., Macintosh, Windows) and browser (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer). This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the Site, pages viewed etc. We use this information to measure the use of our Site and to improve its content.

Email addresses and other personally identifiable information such as first and last name, physical address, telephone number and other similar information are known only when voluntarily provided by a visitor for registration or other participation of visitors in any available online interactive activities.

Unless otherwise disclosed during the data collection process, personally identifiable information that may be collected in connection with visitors to this Site is retained by PDC. We will not sell, transfer or otherwise disclose this personally identifiable information outside this company, except where disclosure is required by law.

We may use the personal information you provide for any of the following purposes: (1) to understand the use of our Site and make improvements; (2) to respond to specific requests from visitors; (3) to obtain parental consent from visitors under 18 years of age, where necessary; (4) to provide any necessary notices to our visitors or their parent or legal guardians, where necessary; (5) to protect the security or integrity of our Site when necessary; (6) to send you notices and solicitations regarding the Site and our businesses; and (7) in general to promote and market products to you. These solicitations may take the form of mailings, telephone calls, e-mail solicitations and other methods of contact. If you do not want to receive these solicitations from us using your personally identifiable information, please notify us.

It is our policy that visitors to our Site who are under the age of 18 should not post or provide information on our Site without the consent of their parents or legal guardians. You should supervise the online activities of your children, and consider the use of parental control tools available from online services and software providers that help provide a child-friendly Internet environment.

At times, we conduct on-line surveys to better understand the needs and profiles of our visitors. When we conduct a survey, we will try to let you know how we will use the information at the time we collect the information from you via the Internet.

This Site may contain links to other sites of third parties. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those other sites. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. You are responsible for checking this policy when you visit our Site to review the current policy. If you do not agree with the policy, you should cease use of the Site immediately.
